hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is Jer M
Kowski in this podcast I talk about ways
for you to grow your coaching or online
course business to be able to scale
things to make the kind of money that
you want to make I help people scale
things from 10 15 $25,000 per month I
built multiple coaching and online
course businesses to over eight figures
that's over $10 million a year and I
want to walk you through how to do it
yourself now I have a premier coaching
program called the client growth
accelerator program would love to have
you in there that's why I actually come
alongside you become a part of your team
and your success strategy to actually
get you results where you're not going
about it on your own you actually get to
work with me to be able to produce those
results for you so jump in there get in
our client go accelerator program and
start to get the results that you
deserve in your business now today we're
going to talk about fighting the right
most profitable Niche or Topic in your
business one of the things that prevents
people from doing this is fomo and fomo
is one of the great killers of a lot of
our dreams a lot of the things that we
should be doing we're afraid of missing
out on opportunities we don't want to
pick the wrong thing and you know
hearing some research recently that um
one of the biggest fears of people is
wasted time putting investment into
something that is not guaranteed and so
human beings we will actually strive and
work really really hard to not do
something that isn't a sure thing or
certain but when it comes to business
unfortunately looking for a sure thing
or certainty doesn't exist there's no
such thing as that so you have to
embrace the uncertainty and actually
understand that that's a big part of it
a big part of business is really merging
the intellectual with the intuition and
that's also where art comes from but in
business business is the art of taking
those things and turning them into a
profit you got to figure out what do
people actually want what is marketable
and what's going to produce money and
the truth is is that it changes over
time because human beings are constantly
in a ation all the time I look at this
like a like a like a box of marbles if
you look at a box of marbles they're all
together and if you shake the Box up
they start to micro rotate what ends up
happening is is in online marketing and
coaching and online courses and all that
the topics of what is the most
profitable is constantly being Shook and
what's happened is the algorithms on
social media are basically shaking that
box of marbles of most profitable niches
and they micro rotate over time and
that's why a profitable
Niche 10 years ago is no longer
profitable today uh but at the same time
it actually morphed and mutated and
turned into other things for instance 10
years ago we were teaching how to do a
lot of the same stuff that we're
teaching today but we weren't teaching
it in the same ways now we have
artificial intelligence and AI is one of
the most powerful tools that can help us
be able to pick the best topics and come
up with things and that's one of the
things I do want to show you is how to
use AI to be able to do that one of the
things that you want to do with AI is
you want it to be a brainstorming tool
you want it to be something that helps
inspire you to be able to think outside
the box to be able to process things to
be able to do things that maybe you
couldn't figure out just on your own now
this isn't about you being unintelligent
or anything like that I mean a lot of
people sometimes they're worried that oh
no I don't want AI to take over me I
don't want AI to replace me I don't want
some kind of an AI to have to think for
me that's not what we're talking about
because with artificial intelligence now
and the way that it works it's kind of
like when Google first came on the scene
Google allowed us to search things
really quickly AI today is essentially
just a hyper focused search engine that
you can really start to um go on a
journey with and discover things much
faster and it knows a lot of information
that's out there and you can start to
ask it questions to really dive into
things and so when you look at it from
that perspective it's really really
powerful that we can use in our
businesses and what's great is it's a
simulator it allows you to
simulate what the market will respond to
it allows you to simulate how the market
will respond so when you're launching
your business when you're trying to
figure out what is the most profitable
Niche or Topic in your
business um the foundational thing to to
look at is
is you got to start from an
experimentation mindset that's number
one you got to start with this idea of
what's called an alpha release approach
where you're testing something out to
see if it's going to to work and this is
again one of those risks that you're
going to have to take you're going to
have to embrace taking risks for you to
be able to reach your goals in your
business if you're not embracing taking
risks you're missing out on a lot of
opportunity a lot of potential to be
able to reach those goals yourself and
so a if we can break past perfectionism
that's huge number two if we can show up
authentically that's also important and
then number three we figure out what are
problems that we can solve for other
people and we can merge those together
we figure out what do I have the ability
to do what is authentic to what my skill
sets are and then how does that align
with problems that other people have and
desires that they have the only reason
anybody's going to buy something from
you is because you solve a problem
because they have a problem that they
are experiencing and you're going to
solve that for them and you're going to
be able to actually take what they are
experiencing and bring a solution to
them very quickly very easily they're
not going to have to struggle through it
and and you're going to be able to save
them a massive amount of
time of trying to figure this stuff out
on their own so in a coaching or online
course business that's one of the
foundations is your ability to produce
transformation in people the reason why
somebody buys from you they become a
client of yours is because they trust in
you your product your company and the
result in transformation that you
promised and you got to become able and
have the confidence and the faith to be
able to and it takes Faith to do this to
be able to make a bold audacious promise
to people of what you're able to
accomplish you know I promise people
that when they jump in my accelerator
program that we will give them the best
coaching the best training the best
resources to be able to reach their
goals to be able to scale their
businesses
and that's exactly what we do on this
podcast we give you the best training
the best resources the best information
to help you get started on your journey
and to solve specific problems in your
life and in your business and it's like
a coaching call it's one of our
reviewers actually said is it's like a
coaching program this podcast is inside
of the podcast if you go through all the
podcast episodes and there's a lot of
episodes of this podcast if you go
through all those episodes they are like
their own coaching program you can get a
lot of value by going through these
episodes I promise you that and I would
recommend that you do so but I'd also
recommend that you jump into our client
grow program if you want to know how to
go beyond just coming up with an idea to
execution and knowing what to execute on
knowing what the Cutting Edge strategies
are that are going to work and knowing
how to produce Financial gains for
yourself and your business it's one
thing to have a great idea something
that you feel passionate about something
that's going to help people but another
to have something that's actually going
to be financially viable and that's
exactly what I love helping people do is
figure out what is financially viable
for them now if we go into AI like chat
GPT and what's awesome is they provided
us now GPT 40 is now free you can use it
anybody can use it it's amazing we can
all you can just jump in and you can
just go to chat.com to access it that's
the new website for chat GPT just go to
chat.com and it pulls it up right
here you can ask any question of chat
GPT and you can see okay what kind of
result answer or outcome is it going to
give me what can I help with you know
what a what a great question it's asking
us right here okay and so we can say I
want to start a online coaching business
but don't know what topic to teach
on okay and what's awesome is when you
can learn to dialogue with AI like
this it's really really going to be able
to help you in a powerful way to be able
to figure a lot of this stuff out
reflect on your experiences and
expertise identify what your passionate
about assess market demand explore
marketable strengths consider your own
challenges and growth now obviously
that's that's like that's okay advice
but what I want to do is I want to dive
deeper can you ask me five powerful
questions to figure out the best Niche
or top topic to go into for a coaching
business okay and I misspelled that and
I actually misspelled it on purpose
because I want you to see it doesn't
really matter that much as far as that
goes so what are the questions what are
unique experiences and challenges that
you've overcome that you feel could
Inspire or guide others on a similar
Journey well I've I've overcome the
ability to create multi-million
doll online course or coaching
businesses
people ask me for advice about getting
more clients and leads and scaling using
Facebook ads okay uh if you could help
others achieve one transformation what
would be I can show them how to take
their idea or desire as a coach or
mentor and have a $10 million or more
business what topic do you see yourself
talking about daily without feeling
drained or bored I love talking about
sales
and and how to sell to people online
then imagine a client reaching
breakthrough what skills tools or
insights uh knowing how to generate
leads run ads and close sales using
webinars okay so those would be like
five different areas for me in my
business that I help people with to be
able to do this and walk them through
and so those answer certain questions to
figure that out okay Niche scaling
online coaching businesses to seven and
eight figures well that's exactly what
we do it's exactly how we help people
building solid sales funnel mastering
lead gen with ads developing effective
webinars sales and conversion tactics
and scaling to multi-million dollar
revenue and by the way that's exactly
what in our accelerator program we help
you do that's exactly what we work with
people on but for your business whatever
your business is you can figure out
different ideas on that by the way
here's another great question watch uh
brain storm 20 possible other niches
that aren't the same as the above but
might leverage my skills okay here's 20
alternative niches uh personal branding
online course creation by the way that's
another thing I talk about a lot with
people high ticket sales Mastery organic
marketing and Lead gen LinkedIn scaling
online webinar strategy digital
marketing for health and wellness we're
we're already niching into that a little
bit right now uh client attention and
upselling scaling freelance business SEO
sales copyrighting and by the way a lot
of this is exactly what we teach in our
courses in my coaching program so it's
it's amazing I was able to unpack a lot
of that to figure some of that out now
let's say you're just starting out and
you don't know what idea to start with
check this out I want to show you
something is could you generate 100
ideas for courses or coaching niches
that I could help people figure out if
if I was mentoring
them to to find the best ones to run on
Facebook ads okay here's a comprehensive
list of what might work out in Facebook
ads um Instagram growth for small
businesses effective time management
Financial Independence for Millennials
productivity coaching meal planning
self-publishing personal branding
debt-free living career transition
website design and the list goes on and
so this gives you us a lot lot of ideas
that you could go based on uh for this
if I switch the model to this one it's
called 01 preview 01 preview has this
reasoning engine where it actually is
going to process and think about a
number of different ideas and formulate
them and what's really cool is it's able
to come up with a number of different
niches that people can be in and by the
way this is exactly a lot of the niches
that our clients are in in their
businesses a lot of our best clients are
in a lot of these different topics or
niches that they help people in so you
could pick any number of these let's say
you're doing um
photography for beginners okay
photography for beginners and you want
to dive deeper into this I could say uh
take this and generate 20 possible sub
niches of this
okay sub niches smartphone photography
for beginners beginner travel
photography okay great awesome uh
generate me and an
eight mod an
eight course coaching program that has
eight topics to teach on
four and watch this it's literally the
AI can help us come up with eight ideas
for different courses traveling
photography fundamentals composition
this could be another course uh let's
see I like this response
better uh creative creative Landscapes
and scenery documented culture and
street photography photographing
landmarks editing editing travel photos
on the go building a
portfolio Okay so those would be ideas
to go based on on that right there
generate me an outline for a coaching
program that I could sell for $997 a
year okay here's the program travel
photography one year 12 months monthly
modules weekly Q&A Community Access
Facebook group monthly challenges and
assignments bonus resources and tools
these are the different months and
modules and how we would teach that okay
so as you can see the AI simulates and
provides us a lot of great ideas that we
could use to be able to come up with a
course or a mentorship program or
something that we could put together now
I would challenge you to create an
account with chat
GPT one of the biggest things that I
find that stops people is they don't
even create an account they haven't even
started to create an account they don't
feel comfortable making using AI they
don't feel comfortable touching it so
can I just challenge you go to chat.com
right now go today go create an account
and start talking with the AI and start
to just play around with it I call it
tossing the ball around playing playing
with the AI the way that like you would
play uh a game have fun with it as far
as that goes and start to get to
experience what it's like like asking AI
these different questions and you can
start to dial in a lot of really cool
stuff in your business now watch this
generate me a sales letter for a
coaching program that is persuasive
informal and conversational in the tone
of Sandy Kowski and Dan Kennedy Okay
sandy Kowski is my mom a lot of the
sales pages that we built were based on
Dan Kennedy and Sandy Kowski this is Dan
Kennedy's book The Ultimate Sales letter
right here and a lot of those sales
Pages for Sandy Kowski I actually wrote
a lot of those myself too so the AI is
trained on some of that by doing this so
what this is doing it's actually
creating this train on a lot of the
style of how I would write sales letters
are you tired of seeing break
breathtaking travel photography on
Instagram and thinking why can't mine
look like that do you wish you could
capture stunning Landscapes and vibrant
Street Scenes what if I told you it
doesn't matter you're just starting out
you can learn to take photos that blow
your friends Minds okay so now if if I
switch the algorithm here improve the
sales letter above I'm going to switch
to 01
preview uh make it more persuasive and
really dial in the sales letter to close
more sales
okay and so that's something that's
really cool now that they've added 01
preview we can generate kind of an
initial version with GPT 40 and then
have 01 preview improve it to really
make it something that is um
much more effective when it comes to
being sales copy and that's what o1
preview is really good at is rewriting
sales letters hello Adventurer have you
stood out a breathtaking Sunset and
thought I wish I could capture this
moment forever what have I told you you
those meth photos into stunning images
yes you absolutely can I get it you're
not a professional photographer maybe
it's your first time with the
camera um introducing travel photography
Master a program capture jaw-dropping
Landscapes tell compelling stories
master your camera edit like a pro build
a studing portfolio this is awesome and
the way that this was able to rewrite it
just with one shot that way is
incredible so again that's the two steps
that I teach people in our
program when you want to create a
coaching program and sell it online you
want to figure out what's the topic
what's the niche and then write some
sales copy and then with that sales copy
you can start to Market to people you
can start to find people you can create
offers online you can generate lead
magnets you can grow your email list and
then start to sell your program to
people that are on that email list that
way by attracting the right people to
you and then walking them through this
process so don't sleep on AI jump into
it I highly recommend getting a copy of
chat gbt plus uh or another one that you
could use is Abacus AI uh Abacus AI is a
great tool chat llm it includes a lot of
different AI algorithms that are built
in into it that you can use and I think
it's a great tool that you can play
around with and use in your business to
get results for you okay
so that's that if you are somebody that
has been trying to grow your business
I'd love to work with you in my client
growth accelerator program move from
just trying to actually getting the
results that you deserve and I'll help
you do that all right very life
everybody we'll talk soon have a good
one
[Applause]
[Music]